[theme music playing]
[Tonio] I'm going to talk.
I started working as Emilia's hit man
when she was still a mayor.
I have a list of the people
she had me kill.
[Ivy] It hurts, Diego, but I
have to stay away from you.
Especially now that my plans
are slowly unfolding.
The party hasn't released
an official list of candidates yet.
There's still so much that can happen.
I am Emilia Ardiente.
I'm destined to be a queen,
and my reign starts today.
-I'm backing out, Senator.
-You can't back out.
Because if you do that,
I will personally make sure
that this is going to be the end
of your political career.
[Arnaldo] It's about Mom.
The party won't be choosing her tonight.
You can always choose another party.
But never your family.
I'm proud to present to you the person
who will complete the senatorial line up.
Mayor Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo.
Governor Emilia will be taking
my grandfather's place.
That is the final decision of the party.
If that's the case,
then we will leave the political party.
[Ivy] Two birds, one stone.
Who's the better hunter now, Mr. Mayor?
-[gunshot]
-[grunts]
[Jepoy] Senator Alcantara was
ambushed. He's dead now.
[Raul] I won't lose you again,
no matter what.
You're mine.
[Ivy] Jepoy, this feels different.
I want to make sure
if my mom really is dead.
[Jepoy] Is it because of your dream?
[Ivy] I want answers to everything.
Because I want the Ardientes to pay
exactly what they owe me.
I want to see Tonio myself.
[Jepoy] Are you ready to face
the person who killed your mother?
[tense music playing]
How many people have you killed
for Emilia Ardiente?
Who are you?
[gunshot]
[grunts, pants]
That's not important.
Do you know everyone you killed?
-[gunshot]
-Ivy.
Do you know Camia Cruz?
Do you remember her?
The woman you raped and murdered?
Do you know her?
So what if I do?
-[gunshot]
-[grunts]
How did you kill Camia Cruz?
Answer me!
How did you kill Camia Cruz?!
-Get out of here.
-Hey!
Lily… Run!
You're the kid that got away.
You're still alive?
Is that why you're interested in all this?
Do you want your children to suffer
the same fate that kid did?
I can do that.
[Ivy] I'll ask again.
How did you…
kill Camia Cruz?
Answer me! How did you kill Camia Cruz?!
How?!
I shot her in the leg.
[grunts]
No!
-[gunshot]
-[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
But she was still breathing
when I buried her in the forest.
[tense music playing]
Are you telling me my mother's alive?
It's possible she's still alive?
Is that right?
My mother is alive?
Is she still alive?
Answer me! Is my mother still alive?!
[Tonio] I don't know.
She'd have to be lucky
to get out of there alive.
You bastard!
You buried my mother alive?!
-You bastard! You monster!
-[gunshots]
[Tonio panting]
How could you do that to my mother?
You have kids, right?
You have a family.
Do you want me to kill them, too?
I'm going to bury all of you alive.
I'll give you a taste
of your own twisted medicine.
No. Please have mercy on me.
Please have mercy.
Forgive me.
I'm begging you. I have a
family! Forgive me.
Forgive you?
I don't know the meaning of that word.
Because what you did to me
and my family does not deserve
to be forgiven!
-But…
-You bastard.
[Tonio] But…
But if your mother is still alive…
it's possible that
the Ardientes might have her.
[tense music playing]
Everyone who's connected to
my family is dying one by one.
First, Mr. Ramon,
and now, Senator Alcantara.
Uncle, what kind of curse
does the Ardiente name
have that requires people to die?
Diego, you can't blame all this
on your family.
No, Uncle.
Try connecting all those people.
They all went against Mom.
My conscience won't stop eating at me…
if I find out Mom
is connected to all this.
Diego, this house you bought is great.
It's nice, huge, well-ventilated.
But, dear, why did you have
to get your own house?
You know you're always
welcome at our place.
Oh, I know!
You're doing this…
because you're not getting
any younger, right?
It looks like you're getting ready…
because you're headed in that direction.
Oh…
You know what I'm talking about.
Well, how's it going? How's Miss Aguas?
With everything that's
happening right now…
I think it'd be selfish of me
if I prioritize my feelings for her.
Besides, just look at
what's happening around us.
The people here are dying one by one.
But…
I'll find time for it.
I'll talk to her.
Good!
[both chuckling]
[Pandoy] Hey. Diego.
-Come on.
-Listen to me.
Um…
You shouldn't give up on love
just because someone else did.
Look at me and your Nanny Loring.
Thump, thump, thump.
[giggling]
It's during times like this
that we need love the most.
That's true.
That's why you shouldn't deprive yourself
and your heart of your right
to love and be happy.
[both chuckling]
You guys are making me jealous.
Let's just go.
We still have a lot of stuff to move.
-You're jealous, huh?
-You should be! Don't hesitate.
[grunts]
[panting]
Jepoy.
There's a chance my mother's still alive.
[panting, sobbing]
My mother could still be alive.
Why is she offering flowers to that girl?
Maybe she thinks they're related,
or maybe she thinks the girl
is her daughter!
I think her memories are returning, Raul.
I have a feeling that my mother
is still alive.
Let me just remind you that we dug up
your mother's remains. I personally--
I know. I know, Jepoy, I know!
But, there's a possibility
that they weren't my mother's remains.
Tonio said so himself.
He said he shot her in the leg…
and buried her alive.
What if that wasn't my mother's body?
That's next to impossible,
Auntie. I doubt it.
Love.
Love, stop that.
You have to rest. You're tired. Come on.
You've been doing this for hours.
Let me just keep these for a while.
You can do this again later.
You're tired. That's enough.
[pensive music playing]
Love, that's enough.
You've been doing this for hours.
You're tired. Just give this to me--
[Camia sobbing]
I told you to stop.
[wailing]
[Belen] Jasmin!
Raul, what's happening to her?
Stop it. Stop.
Jepoy, my heart's telling me…
that my mother's alive.
Jepoy…
I need to find my mother.
I won't stop until I find my mother.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Belen] Jasmin.
[crying]
[instrumental theme music playing]
[Pandoy] It's during times like this
that we need love the most.
Don't deprive yourself
and your heart of your right
to love and be happy.
[Tonio] I shot her in the leg.
But she was still breathing
when I buried her in the forest.
If your mother is still alive,
it's possible that
the Ardientes might have her.
[Arnaldo] No target has ever
escaped my trap.
No matter what happens,
you will be mine, Ivy.
[phone ringing]
[line ringing]
[loud thud]
[murmuring]
-Diego.
-Yes, Nanny?
By the way, I forgot to show you this.
Your copy of the land title
Miss Ivy gave you.
[soft music playing]
-Nanny.
-Yes?
Do you think it's a bad thing…
that Ivy reminds me so much of Lily?
Hmm?
I just noticed they have
so many similarities.
How she pinches Butchoy's cheeks.
How she likes pinwheels.
Her reaction when I took her
to Lily's old house
and the secret garden.
Now this.
What does this mean?
Why is she helping us?
Well, because she's a good person.
I know, Nanny. I know Ivy's a good person.
But why is she always with Mom?
What does she need from my family?
Why is she in Poblacion Ardiente?
Nanny, I have a hunch that Ivy
isn't just here for business.
All right. Let's say that she is Lily.
Then why does she need to pretend?
That's what I have to find out.
[soft music playing]
[exhales sharply]
[phone ringing]
Hello, Vic. Let me talk to Grandpa.
Yes, Mayor.
[monitor beeping]
[sighs] Grandpa, how are you?
Aren't you awake yet?
Well, just to give you an update.
Everything you've worked
so hard for is crumbling down.
Everything.
And Mom, I don't understand her.
All her decisions are questionable.
She could be running us
into the ground, and…
I don't know. I don't know what to do.
I need you.
[pensive music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Natalie wailing]
Daddy!
Why did you leave me?
[sobbing]
I can't handle this.
I need to leave all of this.
I need to go.
What?
You're leaving? What about…
What about your family here?
Daddy's gone now.
I don't have any family left.
Where will you go?
I don't know.
Paris? I don't know.
[sniffles, sobs]
Come here.
I need to go.
I need to forget.
[wailing]
[shushes]
I need to forget.
Help me.
Help me. Help me.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
I'm here.
Stop.
Now that those wretched Alcantaras
are out of our lives…
you can get closer to Ivy now.
Arnaldo, son.
I know that you've been lusting after Ivy
the minute that you laid your eyes on her.
So, we need her now more than ever.
It's a win-win for you and me.
Does this mean
you're letting me pursue Ivy?
You said it yourself, right?
That you're the charm of this family.
So, two birds with one stone.
You know you need her.
And I need her, too.
That's why we need to have her.
Heart rate and pulse rate, all normal.
[suspenseful music playing]
Pupils are dilating normally.
Julio, can you hear me?
If you can hear me, please, nod.
[suspenseful sting]
Emilia, it's good you're here.
Senator Jose is here to see you.
Oh, Senator!
Is there anything that I can do for you?
I'm here to warn you, Emilia.
The party won't stop
until we've caught
whoever had Pablo ambushed.
[gasps]
Senator, are you accusing me?
Maybe I am, Emilia.
I'm really offended, Senator.
You're threatening me in my own house.
I am not afraid of you, Emilia.
What will Julio say
when he recovers and finds out
that you've cut ties with the party
and had his closest friend killed?
You may leave now, Senator Jose.
[dramatic music swelling]
I will make that senator pay.
He'll see.
[phone ringing]
Hello, Dr. York.
Emilia. Good news.
Good news?
Your dad. He's awake.
What?
[Dr. York] You sound so surprised.
[exhales]
I am surprised.
How is he?
He's officially out of the coma.
And his test results are perfect.
He'll be home soon.
You'll be home soon, Julio.
I'm getting impatient, Tonio.
When are you going to give me the list
I've been asking you for?
I'll give you what you want.
I'll help you, on one condition.
Make sure that my family is safe.
Are you serious?!
You're demanding conditions?!
Let me tell you something.
You are in no position to demand anything!
Have mercy on me! I'm begging you!
[scoffs]
Why? Tell me.
Did you show my mother mercy? Did you?
I will never show you any mercy, Tonio.
Not now, not ever.
Are you going to give me what I want,
or do you want me
to have you killed right now?
I will. I will.
What do you mean you will?
Tell me!
I'll give you what you want.
What?
Louder. Say it.
I'll give you what you want.
Very good.
Now we're on the same page.
You didn't have to give me a hard time.
[tense music playing]
Doc.
Why did Jasmin throw a fit like that?
That's actually the first time
that's ever happened.
Does that mean her memories
are coming back?
Is that it?
That's possible.
But it's very rare in her case.
Especially since she suffered
catatonic depression.
And for 13 years,
she was neglected and wasn't
given any medical attention.
Doc, what are the things
that might trigger her memories
of the past to return?
Well, it's possible that this is connected
to what happened to her.
Doc, this all started when
she saw a picture of that woman.
Who is this woman?
How is she connected to Jasmin?
Uh…
She's not, Doc.
What's confusing me now
is why she's so interested in this woman.
Maybe this woman triggers
something from her past.
She probably looks like her mom,
sister, or best friend.
You know what, Raul?
Jasmin's case is very interesting.
If this woman triggers a memory of her,
you should expose her more often,
alongside her electroconvulsive therapy,
so she can get well faster.
Maybe, not now.
I think she only needs a sedative.
That's what she needs to calm down.
Why? Don't you want her to get better?
It's not that.
I just think that some medicine
is enough to help her.
Can you give her a prescription?
Don't worry. I'll give you an update.
Uh, okay. If that's what you want.
Love. Let's go.
Come on.
Thank you, Doc.
Don't worry. I'll keep you posted.
-All right.
-Thank you.
Okay. Thank you.
[tense music playing]
Thank you, Jepoy.
I already gave you what you want.
Please. I'm begging you. My family.
So what if you've given me what I want?
Do you think I'll let you off
the hook just like that?
Just for a book?
Jepoy.
Are you sure about this, Ivy?
What are you gonna do to me?
What are you going to do?
Are you going to kill me
after I helped you?
What would you like?
You want me to thank you?!
Should I be grateful just because of this?
Please, I beg you. Have mercy.
Believe it or not,
I already regret what I did.
Please let me live. Please…
I'll do everything you want.
Have mercy.
Stand up!
I said stand up and sit!
Right now, I don't feel sorry for you…
because you deserve to die.
I really want to kill you,
but I don't want soil my hands
with your dirty blood.
So you should be thankful.
Have mercy on me.
Have mercy on my family.
I regret what I did.
Jepoy, you know what to do.
Don't kill me. Don't kill me.
Let me live. I'll do anything you want.
Jepoy, make sure you give him…
everything he wants before you kill him.
No! Have mercy! Please!
Boss.
Boss, have mercy on me.
-Back away.
-Boss, please, let me live.
Think about my family.
Dad?
Dad!
-Sweetheart!
-Dad!
Dad!
What will happen when Papa comes back?
They're going to treat me
like trash again!
All my plans will be for nothing.
I'm going to be miserable again.
Papa will have Raul killed.
This family is over!
Calm down, Emilia.
You're stronger than this.
You can fix this.
You're right, Auntie.
Papa has no reason to return here.
Or he shouldn't return at all.
You deserve to be
where you are now, Emilia.
You worked hard for all this.
And I don't think Julio
has a place in this house…
or in this town…
or in your life.
[Arnaldo] Mom!
We need to talk.
Why didn't you tell me
Grandpa's recovered?
I spoke to his doctor.
He said he already told you.
Arnaldo, I was about to tell you.
-But now that you know--
-Oh! Stop it.
You're too obvious.
You aren't happy he's awake now.
How dare you!
Are you saying that I was happy
when Papa slipped into a coma?
I love him more than you know.
You do?
Then why did you never
visit him in America?
[clicks tongue, exhales]
Don't worry.
I'll tell Grandpa you were so busy
taking over for him here.
I'm going to bring him home.
[door slams shut]
Let's just wait for the results
of the DNA test after two days.
Two days?
Two days is too long.
I need the results in 24 hours.
Can you do it, Mr. Valenzuela?
Twenty-four hours?
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you.
Jepoy, please see him out.
[exhales]
Nanny, I can't wait any longer.
I need to know the truth.
-Ivy…
-Emilia…
If my mom is still alive,
that doesn't mean
I'll let her off the hook.
Emilia will still rot in jail.
All of them.
All the Ardientes will rot in jail.
I know, Ivy.
[exhales]
[Raul] Auntie, I don't like this.
Her memories can't return.
This might be better for her…
to be Jasmin for the rest of her life.
Don't you feel sorry for her, Raul?
She'd be more miserable
if she remembers everything
that happened in her life.
[phone ringing]
-Hello.
-Raul.
You need to come home now,
or I'll send my men after you.
All right. Fine.
[soft music playing]
If I could take away
all the pain you feel…
But how can I do that…
if you're hiding so many secrets from me?
[tense music playing]
[grunting]
-Hey! What do you want?!
-Ow!
[grunting]
[tense music playing]
Diego?
[grunting]
Who ordered you to do this? Who?
Senator Alcantara's daughter. Natalie.
Dude, run!
Hey!
Diego!
That stupid Natalie.
I don't have time for her.
That witch.
Are you sure you're okay?
Did you break anything?
[soft music playing]
Ivy, I'm sorry. They got away.
Diego, why are you apologizing?
You don't have to.
I should thank you.
Thank you for coming to save me.
But Natalie…
[sighs] I don't know why Natalie did that.
But she'll get what she deserves
one of these days.
Maybe not now, but soon enough.
But you have to be careful, Ivy.
You should tighten your security.
Diego, thank you.
But I can take care of myself.
Uh…
What made you come here?
Is there something you need?
Uh…
I don't know, Ivy.
I don't know why my feet led me here.
I should get going now.
Diego.
Thanks again.
Be careful.
Did you hear me, Raul?
I said Papa is awake.
I know.
Then why do you look so calm?
In case you've forgotten,
you're the one who strangled him.
Emilia, I will never forget that day.
Are you making fun of me, Raul?
Once Papa orders your death,
I don't know how
I can get you out of that.
If there's someone who should
be worried, it's you, not me.
After all the mistakes you've made…
I'm sure your father will go
after you first.
But you have a solution for that, right?
Just have him killed.
[suspenseful music playing]
-Raul.
-What?
Who is Jasmin?
Jasmin? I don't know who that is.
You liar! Stop fooling me! What's this?!
-Who's Jasmin?!
-Oh, come on!
Who's Jasmin?
What are you talking about? What Jasmin?
So what's that?
Do you know where I got this?
I went to a gas station
and used their bathroom.
I used this to wipe myself.
Here, smell it.
Stop it! Stop fooling me! Who's Jasmin?!
If you won't tell me who your whore is,
I'll find her myself!
If you want, I'll even help you!
Here.
Problem solved.
Why did you do that?! You bastard!
Stop it, Emilia.
Instead of thinking about some name,
you should worry about your father.
Because he's going to take
everything you have right now.
[shower door slams shut]
[tense music playing]
Ivy.
Ivy, Mr. Valenzuela's here.
He brought the DNA test results.
Miss Aguas.
Thank you.
Please, show him out.
-You're welcome.
-This way, sir.
[instrumental theme music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
[exhales]
[gasping]
There's a chance…
There's a chance Mom's still alive.
[exhales sharply]
My mom could still be alive.
Mom.
My mom.
You might still be alive.
You might still be alive, Mom.
Mom, I'll find you, wherever you are.
I'm going to find you, Mom,
so we can be together.
Mom…
My mom is still alive.
Ivy. Ivy.
[instrumental theme music
continues playing]
There's a chance my mother's alive.
There's a big chance
she's still out there.
There's a huge chance my mother
is still alive, Nanny Carlotta.
I want to see my mom.
I need to find her.
I need to find my mother.
I'm going to find her.
[dramatic music playing]
-Mom.
-Lily.
[gasps]
[Camia cries]
[groaning]
[screaming]
Ivy? Ivy.
-Jepoy.
-Why? What happened?
Jepoy.
Why? What's wrong?
Jepoy, look.
Negative.
Jepoy, negative.
My hunch was right all along.
My dream was right.
I'm even more convinced
my mother is still alive.
[breathing heavily]
Lily?
Lily? [gasps]
Jepoy.
Jepoy, please help me.
I need you even more now.
Help me. We need to find my mom.
Jepoy.
There's a huge chance
my mother is still alive.
We'll do everything we can
to find your mother.
[quietly] My mom is alive.
I'm going to find her.
My mom is alive.
Mom, I'm going to find you.
[crying] Lily.
Lily.
Jasmin?
Who is Lily?
[dramatic music playing]
Let's start with the Ardientes.
It's possible they're hiding my mother.
I know that she's still here
Poblacion Ardiente.
I'll keep an eye out for her.
I'll even investigate
in the other towns if I have to.
Good.
[Ivy] Where's my mom?
I told you to bring her to me.
[Valenzuela]
Let's just wait for the results
of the DNA test after two days.
[Ivy] I need the results in 24 hours.
Jepoy, where did you find those
remains we thought were hers?
In the place where Tonio said
he buried your mom.
Jepoy, someone took my mom.
Someone took her,
replaced her with another body,
and put this ring on it,
just to fake her death.
It's possible only one person
is behind all this.
All this time, Jepoy,
all this time, my mom was alive!
Jepoy, this is what you'll do.
I want you to investigate that corpse.
Find out who she was and who took her.
Because I'm sure
that person has my mother.
-Auntie?
-Hey, Raul.
[Raul] How are you?
It's good that she's feeling better now.
How is she? Is she still
fiddling with those newspapers?
Not anymore. She's quiet now.
But she was talking last night.
What was she saying?
[pensive music playing]
Lily.
Lily?
Any updates, Jepoy?
Ivy, I have the profile of all
the missing persons here in the town.
This is from the police.
I'm going to ask around to see
which of these people have been
missing for a long time now.
One of them must have been used
as the decoy
to replace your mom's remains.
Thank you. Thank you, Jepoy.
I know this is an arduous process.
But we'll learn the truth eventually.
I'm going to ask around, too.
And I'll start with
the most powerful house here.
Emilia.
If she had my mom killed before…
I have a hunch
that my mom might be
in her custody if she survived.
What's your plan?
It's simple.
Just like what you did with that corpse…
I'm going to dig up
all of Emilia's skeletons
and bring her fears to life.
Ivy, can you repeat what you said?
You're going to help me
with my image building?
Yes.
Grassroots campaign, Emilia.
The Filipinos will slowly get to know
and love Emilia Ardiente-Torillo.
Just tell me when.
And I'm going to send
my team of experts over.
Oh! Thank you, Ivy.
That's one great news.
And that's just what I need right now.
Right after hearing the terrible news.
What terrible news?
Well, Papa's health is improving.
He's coming back home.
And that means my happy days are over.
Then that means we need to
speed up your candidacy, Emilia.
Why don't we release
a magazine article about you?
The more controversial, the better.
So, tell me, Emilia.
What's the darkest past
of Emilia's administration?
[exhales]
Well, let's just say I've made
a lot of decisions in life
that I didn't think through.
That destroyed people's lives.
Like what?
Whose lives did you destroy, Emilia?
Come on. You can tell me.
You've already told me
so many secrets before.
You can trust me. Promise.
This family.
All of them wiped out.
But that was 13 years ago.
It was too long ago that even
God may have forgotten about it.
Don't you think, Ivy?
[tense music playing]
You had a whole family murdered?
Not a single one survived?
The whole family.
Because when I tell my men
to do a good job…
it is indeed a good job.
Hold on.
Why are you so curious
about that family's story?
Why all of a sudden, Ivy?
[tense music playing]
[Tonio] I only killed the victims.
But I'm not the one who buried them.
-Who did?
-Mr. Noel.
Who told you to do it?
It was Raul. Raul Torillo.
Who told you to take over
everything I left behind?
You have no right sitting
in my goddamn chair!
You're going to have Julio killed?
Poblacion Ardiente is too small
for the both of us.
-It's your son's birthday.
-Yeah, I know.
[Ivy] So, let's have fun?
Hello?
[theme music playing]